Register of the Warren Christopher papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Videorecordings, 1992-2008
  - VHS videocassettes, 1992-2006
    - ABC Good Morning America program appearance, 2001 (Box-folder 43: 13)
    - "Chances of a Lifetime", 2001 (Box-folder 43: 14)
    - PBS Newshour interviews with Jim Lehrer, 1996-2001 (Box-folder 44: 1-4)
    - "Jimmy Carter: An Hour before Daylight", 2001 (Box-folder 44: 5)
    - Judge Stanley Mosk, 2003 (Box-folder 44: 6)
    - KCET interview and Joseph Lieberman acceptance speech, 2000 (Box-folder 44: 7)
    - Larry King Live program appearance, 2002 (Box-folder 44: 8)
    - NBC Today Show appearance, 1994 (Box-folder 44: 9)
    - ABC Nightline program appearance in relation to Iran's nuclear program, 1992 (Box-folder 44: 10)
    - Bill Clinton greeting to Center for Law and Public Interest dinner, 2001 (Box-folder 44: 11)
    - United States Information Service conference, 1994 (Box-folder 44: 12)
    - "Remarkable Women of the 20th Century", 1999 (Box-folder 44: 13)
    - Rocky Delgadillo, 2001 (Box-folder 44: 14)
    - "Russia and the Other Former Soviet Republics in Transition", 1998 (Box-folder 44: 15)
    - Press conference on Middle East peace talks, 1993 (Box-folder 45: 1)
    - Testimony before Senate Appropriations Committee, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 45: 2-3)
    - Testimony before Senate Foreign Relations Committee, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 45: 4-14)
    - The Daily Show with Jon Stewart appearance (Box-folder 46: 1-2)
    - Speech in Chicago, 1993 (Box-folder 46: 3)
    - Speech on environmental policy at Stanford University, 1996 (Box-folder 46: 4)
    - European trip, 1993 (Box-folder 46: 5)
    - Trip to Asia and Middle East, 1993 (Box-folder 46: 6)
    - Trip to G-7 economic summit in Halifax, Nova Scotia, Canada, 1993 (Box-folder 46: 7)
    - State Department portrait unveiling, 1999 (Box-folder 46: 8)
    - Bill Moyers program, "Trading Democracy", 2002 (Box-folder 46: 9-10)
    - Tavis Smiley program appearance, 2006 (Box-folder 46: 11)
    - Annual reports of the Secretaries of State, 1998-2002 (Box-folder 46: 12-15)
    - This Week with David Brinkley program appearance, 1996 (Box-folder 47: 1)
    - "United States Foreign Policy Priorities on the Eve of the 21st Century," speech, Rice University, 1997 (Box-folder 47: 2-3)
    - Town meeting with regional media, 1996 (Box-folder 47: 4)
    - History Channel program on Chances of a Lifetime, 2001 (Box-folder 47: 5)
    - C-SPAN program on The Tides of War, 2000 (Box-folder 47: 6)
    - Together for Peace Foundation awards, 1995 (Box-folder 47: 7)
    - Between the Lines program with Gavin De Becker and Julia Sweeney, 1997 (Box-folder 47: 8)
    - "What is Croatia, Anyway?", 1992 (Box-folder 47: 9)
    - Thomas Friedman on The Lexus and the Olive Tree, 1999 (Box-folder 47: 10)
    - "Visiting...with Huell Howser", 1995 (Box-folder 47: 12)
- Audio recordings on compact sound cassettes, 1993-2001
  - Speech in Hamburg, Germany, 1993 (Box-folder 47: 13)
  - Speech by Bill Clinton, 1996 (Box-folder 47: 14)
  - WNYC interview, 2001 (Box-folder 47: 15)
  - Milt Rosenberg Extension 720 program, 2001 (Box-folder 47: 16)
  - Diane Rehm program, 2001 (Box-folder 47: 17)